Before we calculate how much non-standard paper was sold,
قبل أن نحسب كمية الورق غير القياسي الذي تم بيعه،
let's check out the order quantities in each column of the orders table.
دعونا نتحقق من كميات الطلب في كل عمود في جدول الطلبات.
Now let's create a new column that adds poster and gloss
لنقم الآن بإنشاء عمود جديد يضيف ملصقًا
paper together to create a field for nonstandard paper.
وورق اللمعان معًا لإنشاء حقل للورق غير القياسي.
To do this, we'll create a new line in the query and use an arithmetic operator.
للقيام بذلك، سنقوم بإنشاء سطر جديد في الاستعلام واستخدام عامل حسابي.
You'll notice that the values in this new column are equal to the sum
ستلاحظون أن القيم في هذا العمود الجديد تساوي مجموع
of the gloss and poster quantities on a row-by-row basis.
كميات ورق اللمعان والملصقات على أساس كل صف على حدة.
In the first row, 22 gloss and 24
في الصف الأول، 22 ورقة لمعان و 24
poster sum to 46 nonstandard in this new column we've created.
ملصقًا بإجمالي 46 ورقة غير قياسية في هذا العمود الجديد الذي أنشأناه.
There's a special name for this.
هناك اسم خاص لهذا.
It's a derived column.
إنه عمود مشتق.
Derived columns can include simple arithmetic or any number of advanced calculations.
يمكن أن تتضمن الأعمدة المشتقة حسابًا بسيطًا أو أي عدد من العمليات الحسابية المتقدمة.
What makes them special is the fact that they're not
ما يجعلهم مميزين هو حقيقة أنهم لا يتم
just directly selected from the underlying data,
اختيارهم مباشرة من البيانات الأساسية،
they're manipulated in some way.
بل يتم التلاعب بهم بطريقة ما.
Rather than stick with this ugly column name,
بدلاً من التمسك باسم العمود القبيح هذا،
let's add something more descriptive using an alias.
دعونا نضيف شيئًا أكثر وصفية باستخدام اسم مستعار.
We can do this by adding AS to the end of the line that
يمكننا القيام بذلك عن طريق إضافة AS إلى نهاية السطر الذي
produces the derived column and then giving it a name.
يُنتج العمود المشتق ومن ثم نعطيه اسماً.
The best practice here is to use names that are clearly descriptive,
تتمثل أفضل الممارسات هنا في استخدام الأسماء الوصفية بوضوح،
follow existing conventions, and don't include capital letters or spaces.
واتباع المواثيق الحالية ، وعدم إدراج أحرف كبيرة أو مسافات.
We'll use non-standard quantity.
سنستخدم كمية غير قياسية.